SHELDON:
Why hast thou forsaken me, O
deity whose existence I doubt?
(Policeman:)Here. Breathe
into this bag.
(Leonard:)What's going on?
They stole everything, Leonard!
(Sheldon:)Everything.
(Policeman:)Are you the roommate?
(Leonard:)Yeah, Leonard Hofstadter.
What happened?
(Policeman:)Your friend here called 911
to report a robbery.
(Leonard:)Oh, my God,
what did they get?
(Sheldon:)What didn't they get?
(Sheldon:)They got my enchanted weapons,
my vicious gladiator armor,
(Sheldon:)my wand of untainted power,
and all my gold!
(Leonard:)You called the police
(Leonard:)because someone hacked your
World of Warcraft account?
(Sheldon:)What choice did I have?
(Sheldon:)The mighty Sheldor,
level 85 blood elf,
(Sheldon:)hero of the Eastern kingdoms,
(Sheldon:)has been picked clean, like
a carcass in the desert sun.
(Sheldon:)Plus, the FBI hung up on me.
(wheezing)
(Policeman:)Into the bag.